<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Documentation</title><link>http://documentation-securonix.github.io/doc/docs/example/Content-Management/</link><description>Recent content on Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://documentation-securonix.github.io/doc/docs/example/Content-Management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>http://documentation-securonix.github.io/doc/docs/example/Content-Management/Deploy_Content/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://documentation-securonix.github.io/doc/docs/example/Content-Management/Deploy_Content/</guid><description>Deploy Content # When you download content using Content Management, the local content folder is updated. If any new content is available, it is displayed in the content category. You have to deploy the content before you can use it in SNYPR.
You can download and deploy the content from the Securonix content library using Menu &amp;gt; Admin &amp;gt; Content Management. The Content Update screen is displayed.
The Content Update screen provides the following:</description></item><item><title/><link>http://documentation-securonix.github.io/doc/docs/example/Content-Management/Commit_Content/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://documentation-securonix.github.io/doc/docs/example/Content-Management/Commit_Content/</guid><description>Commit Content # When you commit your content, all information required for selected policies and parsers are committed. However, you can decide if you want to commit any supporting information or not. The supporting information for policies are tier-2 checks and workflow, and for parser is data dictionary.
Committing Policy # To commit policies to the Securonix content library, perform the following:
Navigate to Menu &amp;gt; Admin &amp;gt; Content Management.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://documentation-securonix.github.io/doc/docs/example/Content-Management/New_Features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://documentation-securonix.github.io/doc/docs/example/Content-Management/New_Features/</guid><description>New Features # Customers don’t have an option to update customized securonix OOTB parsers. Application lacks ownership tracking of the parser at a granular level.
Resource groups require a certain level of customization specific to a customer or tenant. Eg: Geolocation Enrichment, IP Attribution, TPI enrichment,etc. Improved parser data flow and content management deploy logic allows the users to retain the Customer created content and receive updates to Securonix created content.</description></item></channel></rss>