<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Documentation</title><link>http://documentation-securonix.github.io/doc/docs/example/Synpr-Content/</link><description>Recent content on Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://documentation-securonix.github.io/doc/docs/example/Synpr-Content/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>http://documentation-securonix.github.io/doc/docs/example/Synpr-Content/Getting_Started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://documentation-securonix.github.io/doc/docs/example/Synpr-Content/Getting_Started/</guid><description>Commit Content # SNYPR content is categorized by functionality. Functionality is a category that defines a datasource type. For example: Web Proxy is a functionality and Blue Coat Proxy is a datasource. By categorizing datasources by functionality, SNYPR can apply similar parsers, policies, and threat models to all datasources with similar functionality.
The functionality determines what content is available when you import the datasource. For a list of functionality supported by SNYPR, see Supported Functionality.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://documentation-securonix.github.io/doc/docs/example/Synpr-Content/Connectors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://documentation-securonix.github.io/doc/docs/example/Synpr-Content/Connectors/</guid><description>Connectors # SNYPR provides out-of-box connectors to import activity events from various datasources. Before you can setup the ingestion process, you have to check if an out-of-box connector is available for the datasource. There are three scenarios that can occur:
The out-of-box connector is available. The out-of-box connector is available but parser is not available. The out-of-box connector is not available.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://documentation-securonix.github.io/doc/docs/example/Synpr-Content/Data-dictionary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://documentation-securonix.github.io/doc/docs/example/Synpr-Content/Data-dictionary/</guid><description>Data Dictionary # Data Dictionary simplifies the ingestion, analytics, and hunting processes by providing consistent and easy to understand labels for data ingested from various datasources. These labels provide uniformity to data ingested from multiple datasources within a functionality.
Content developers can use these mapped labels to create policies that can be used for multiple datasources. This reduces the time and effort a content developer has to spend on creating policies for different datasources.</description></item></channel></rss>